A Register of the Records of the Russkaia sredniaia shkola (Paris, France)Records
Hoover Institution Archives
- Office file, 1920-1997 and undated. (Box 1)
  - Student records
    - Sal'skii, Boris (Folder 29: 29)
    - Samarin, Mikhail, and Ul'iana (Folder 29: 30)
    - Samin, A. (Folder 29: 31)
    - Samoilenko, Aleksandr (Folder 29: 32)
    - Samson-Gimmelstern, Aleksei (Folder 29: 33)
    - Samsonov, Igor', Viktor (Folder 29: 34)
    - Sanina, Kira (Folder 29: 35)
    - Sapunova, Nadezhda (Folder 29: 36)
    - Sarach, Mikhail (Folder 29: 37)
    - Saraf, Aleksandr (Folder 29: 38)
    - Sarangor, Aleksandr (Folder 29: 39)
    - Sarkisian, Taisiia, and Tamara (Folder 29: 40)
    - Sarukhanova, Suzanne (Folder 29: 41)
    - Sass-Tissovskaia, Galina, and Rimma (Folder 29: 42)
    - Satina, Mariia (Folder 29: 43)
    - Savchenko, Georgii (Folder 29: 44)
    - Savchenko, Taras (Folder 29: 45)
    - Savichev, Sergei (Folder 29: 46)
    - Savina, Ol'ga (Folder 29: 47)
    - Savitskaia, Tat'iana (Folder 29: 48)
    - Savranskaia, Ivonna (Folder 29: 49)
    - Sazonova, Vera (Folder 29: 50)
    - Sechko, Mikhail (Folder 29: 51)
    - Sedashov, Evgenii (Folder 29: 52)
    - Sedergolian, Petr (Folder 29: 53)
    - Sailan'ian, Libarit (Folder 29: 54)
    - Sekretov, Sergei (Folder 29: 55)
    - Seletskaia, Elena (Folder 29: 56)
    - Selitskii, Aleksei (Folder 29: 57)
    - Semenov, Igor' (Folder 29: 58)
    - Semenov, Petr-Nikolai, and Sergei (Folder 29: 59)
    - Semenov, Valentin (Folder 29: 60)
    - Semenova, Anna (Folder 29: 61)
    - Semenova, Elizaveta (Folder 29: 62)
    - Seregina, Larisa (Folder 29: 63)
    - Serebriakov, Mikhail, and Sergei (Folder 29: 64)
    - Serensen, Galina (Folder 29: 65)
    - Serikov, Aleksei (Folder 29: 66)
    - Sergeeva, Sofiia (Folder 29: 67)
    - Sev, Sofiia (Folder 29: 68)
    - Shagal, Tat'iana (Folder 29: 69)
    - Sharpin, Martin (Folder 29: 70)
    - Sharron, Eric (Folder 29: 71)
    - Shcheglov, Aleksandr, and Ivan (Folder 29: 72)
    - Shcherbakov, Aleksandr, and Iurii, and Nikolai, and Petr, and Viacheslav (Folder 29: 73)
    - Shcherbin, Mikhail (Folder 29: 74)
    - Shchupliak, Igor', and Robert (Folder 29: 75)
    - Shchurevich, Ol'ga, and Zinaida (Folder 29: 76)
    - Shchurov, Vladimir (Folder 29: 77)
    - Sheideker, Alan (Folder 29: 78)
    - Shishman, Valentin (Folder 29: 79)
    - Shishmareva, Irina (Folder 29: 80)
    - Shklovskii, Grigorii (Folder 29: 81)
    - Shliapnikova, Tat'iana (Folder 29: 82)
    - Shpakovich, Boris (Folder 29: 83)
    - Shpilevskii, Nikolai (Folder 29: 84)
    - Shpil'nichenko, Vladimir (Folder 29: 85)
    - Shrira, Solomon (Folder 29: 86)
    - Shvabo, Igor', and Oleg, and Marina (Folder 29: 87)
    - Shteding, Elena (Box-folder 30: 1)
    - Shtein, Andrei, and Elena, and Georgii, and Liudmila, and Sergei (Folder 30: 2)
    - Shtern, Iosif (Folder 30: 3)
    - Shtertsel', Anatolii (Folder 30: 4)
    - Shtiglits, Viktoriia (Folder 30: 5)
    - Shtorkh, Nataliia (Folder 30: 6)
    - Shukher, Izrail' (Folder 30: 7)
    - Shul'gin, Vadim (Folder 30: 8)
    - Shul'zhenko, Tat'iana (Folder 30: 9)
    - Shumakher, Evgeniia (Folder 30: 10)
    - Shupinskii, Konstantin (Folder 30: 11)
    - Shushkevich, Vladimir (Folder 30: 12)
    - Shuvalov, Petr (Folder 30: 13)
    - Shuvalova, Elena, and Nataliia (Folder 30: 14)
    - Sichenko, Petr (Folder 30: 15)
    - Sidorina, Nina (Folder 30: 16)
    - Sidorov, Aleksandr (Folder 30: 17)
    - Sidorov, Georgii (Folder 30: 18)
    - Silenko, Roman (Folder 30: 19)
    - Simonov, Gavriil (Folder 30: 20)
    - Simonova, Aleksandra (Folder 30: 21)
    - Siniaev, Vladimir (Folder 30: 22)
    - Sinitskaia, Ol'ga (Folder 30: 23)
    - Sionskaia-Naumova, Nataliia (Folder 30: 24)
    - Sitnikova, Nataliia (Folder 30: 25)
    - Skachkovskaia, Irina (Folder 30: 26)
    - Skalon, Tamara, and Tat'iana (Folder 30: 27)
    - Skliarenko, Ol'ga (Folder 30: 28)
    - Skobtsov, Georgii (Folder 30: 29)
    - Skrotskii, Nikolai (Folder 30: 30)
    - Slatin, Aleksei (Folder 30: 31)
    - Sliozberg, Anatolii (Folder 30: 32)
    - Sliusarchuk, Petr (Folder 30: 33)
    - Sliusarev, Sergei (Folder 30: 34)
    - Slepovran-Lopatinskii, Georgii (Folder 30: 35)
    - Smetankin, Andrei, and Grigorii (Folder 30: 36)
    - Smirnov, Aleksandr, and Georgii, and Iakov (Folder 30: 37)
    - Smirnova, Anastasiia (Folder 30: 38)
    - Smirnova, Ekaterina, Ol'ga (Folder 30: 39)
    - Smirnova, Elena (Folder 30: 40)
    - Smitten, Sergei (Folder 30: 41)
    - Smolenskaia (Advokatova), Elizaveta (Folder 30: 42)
    - Smolenskii, Vladimir (Folder 30: 43)
    - Smul'skii, Sergei (Folder 30: 44)
    - Snarskii, Vladislav (Folder 30: 45)
    - Sobarnitskaia, Mariia (Folder 30: 46)
    - Sobstianskii, O. (Folder 30: 47)
    - Sokolenko, Evgenii (Folder 30: 48)
    - Sokol'nikov, Liudmila, and Militsa, and Sergei (Folder 30: 49)
    - Sokolov, Boris, and Evgeniia, and Nikolai, and Sergei, and Tat'iana, and Vadim, and Vera (Folder 30: 50)
    - Sokolovskaia, Nataliia, and Margarita (Folder 30: 51)
    - Sokol'skii, Nikolai (Folder 30: 52)
    - Sokorovskii, Ivan (Folder 30: 53)
    - Solanzh, Sigal' (Folder 30: 54)
    - Sollogub-Shofeld, Anton (Folder 30: 55)
    - Sollogub, Irina (Folder 30: 56)
    - Sollogub, Konstantin (Folder 30: 57)
    - Sollogub, Vladimir (Folder 30: 58)
    - Solodovnikov, Ekaterina, and Elizaveta, and Nataliia (Folder 30: 59)
    - Solodovnikov, Petr (Folder 30: 60)
    - Solodovnikov, Tat'iana (Folder 30: 61)
    - Soloveichik, Nataliia (Folder 30: 62)
    - Solov'ev, Andrei, and Ivan, and Sergei, and Stepan (Folder 30: 63)
    - Solov'eva, Irina, and Jacqueline (Folder 30: 64)
    - Solovskaia, Mariia (Folder 30: 65)
    - Somov, Mikhail (Folder 30: 66)
    - Sopova, Irina, and Lidiia (Folder 30: 67)
    - Sorechinskii, Iurii (Folder 30: 68)
    - Sorkin, Georgii (Folder 30: 69)
    - Sorokin, Andrei (Folder 30: 70)
    - Sozanovich, Aleksandr (Folder 30: 71)
    - Spasskii, Georgii (Folder 30: 72)
    - Spasskii, Nikolai (Folder 30: 73)
    - Speranskaia, Irina (Folder 30: 74)
    - Srechinskii, Georgii (Folder 30: 75)
    - Stamboli, Era, and Lidiia (Folder 30: 76)
    - Stamogmu, Aristid (Folder 30: 77)
    - Starchenko, Mikhail (Folder 30: 78)
    - Stargentskii, Irina (Folder 30: 79)
    - Stark, Sergei (Folder 30: 80)
    - Starodvorskaia, Aleksandra (Box-folder 31: 1)
    - Stavraki, Vadim (Folder 31: 2)
    - Stefanova, Irina, and Iuliia, and Valentina (Folder 31: 3)
    - Stefanovich, Elizaveta (Folder 31: 4)
    - Steiner, Irina (Folder 31: 5)
    - Stepanov, Vladimir (Folder 31: 6)
    - Stepanova, Irina (Folder 31: 7)
    - Stepurenko, Vladimir (Folder 31: 8)
    - Stetsenko, Irina (Folder 31: 9)
    - Stevens, Elena (Folder 31: 10)
    - Stoborova, Tat'iana (Folder 31: 11)
    - Stopari, Georgii (Folder 31: 12)
    - Strakach, Elena (Folder 31: 13)
    - Strakhovich, Andrei, and Kirill (Folder 31: 14)
    - Strand, Ekaterina, and Elizaveta (Folder 31: 15)
    - Strankovskaia, Mariia (Folder 31: 16)
    - Strannoliubskii, Aleksei (Folder 31: 17)
    - Strepkova, Irina (Folder 31: 18)
    - Struve, Georgii (Folder 31: 19)
    - Struve, Tat'iana (Folder 31: 20)
    - Stul'ba, Ivan (Folder 31: 21)
    - Stulov, Mariia, and Pavel, and Timofei (Folder 31: 22)
    - Sudakov, Sergei (Folder 31: 23)
    - Sudoplatov, Vladimir (Folder 31: 24)
    - Sukhanov, Mikhail, and Ol'ga (Folder 31: 25)
    - Sulatskii, Aleksei (Folder 31: 26)
    - Sultan-Girei, Ella (Folder 31: 27)
    - Surazhskaia, Inga, and Nina (Folder 31: 28)
    - Surkova, Nesta (Folder 31: 29)
    - Suvorov, Nikolai (Folder 31: 30)
    - Suzdal'tseva, Liudmila, and Zinaida (Folder 31: 31)
    - Sviatopolk-Mirskii, Sergei (Folder 31: 32)
    - Svistunov, Onisim (Folder 31: 33)
    - Taranovskii, Petr (Folder 31: 34)
    - Tarasenkova, Ol'ga (Folder 31: 35)
    - Tarasevich, Vadim (Folder 31: 36)
    - Tarasov, Mikhail (Folder 31: 37)
    - Tarasova, Colette (Folder 31: 38)
    - Tarkhanova, Ekaterina (Folder 31: 39)
    - Tasso, Dominque, and Gilbert, and Mikhail (Folder 31: 40)
    - Tatarinov, Nadezhda, and Nataliia, and Vsevolod (Folder 31: 41)
    - Tatarova, Aleksandra (Folder 31: 42)
    - Tatishcheva, Mariia (Folder 31: 43)
    - Taube, Sergei (Folder 31: 44)
    - Tenenbaum, Nukhim (Folder 31: 45)
    - Teper, Lazar' (Folder 31: 46)
    - Ter-Gabriliants, Iakov (Folder 31: 47)
    - Ter-Mikelev, Mikhail (Folder 31: 48)
    - Ter-Sarkisov, Leon (Folder 31: 49)
    - Terebinskii, Sergei (Folder 31: 50)
    - Terent'ev, Aleksandr, and Mikhail (Folder 31: 51)
    - Tertseva, Alisa (Folder 31: 52)
    - Tesliukova, Ekaterina (Folder 31: 53)
    - Tetar, Marcel (Folder 31: 54)
    - Tikhobrazov, Boris (Folder 31: 55)
    - Tikhomirov, Mikhail (Folder 31: 56)
    - Tikhomirov, Nikolai (Folder 31: 57)
    - Tikhomirova, Ol'ga (Folder 31: 58)
    - Tikhonitskii, Vadim, and Marianna (Folder 31: 59)
    - Tikhonov, Pavel (Folder 31: 60)
    - Tikhonova, Tat'iana (Folder 31: 61)
    - Till, Tamara (Folder 31: 62)
    - Tillo, Pavel, and Petr (Folder 31: 63)
    - Tillot, Georgii de, and Liudmila de, and Nikolai de (Folder 31: 64)
    - Timchenko, Evgenii (Folder 31: 65)
    - Timchenko, Mariia (Folder 31: 66)
    - Tin'el, Igor' (Folder 31: 67)
    - Tirtova, Kira (Folder 31: 68)
    - Titov, Aleksandr (Folder 31: 69)
    - Tiutchev, Vladimir (Folder 31: 70)
    - Tizengauzen, Orest (Folder 31: 71)
    - Tkachenko, Boris (Folder 31: 72)
    - Tkachenko, Pavel (Folder 31: 73)
    - Tkachev, Ivan (Folder 31: 74)
    - Tolchinskaia, Liudmila (Folder 31: 75)
    - Tolli, Marianna (Folder 31: 76)
    - Tolstoi, Il'ia (Folder 31: 77)
    - Tolstoi, Pavel (Folder 31: 78)
    - Tolstoi-Miloslavskii, Vladimir (Folder 31: 79)
    - Tomas-Brus, Eremei (Folder 31: 80)
    - Topuria, Tamara (Folder 31: 81)
    - Topchii, Boris (Folder 31: 82)
    - Toropov, Aleksei, and Igor' (Folder 31: 83)
    - Torrens, Tat'iana (Folder 31: 84)
    - Trakhtereva, Tat'iana (Folder 31: 85)
    - Tregubov, Nikolai (Folder 31: 86)
    - Treskin, Igor' (Folder 31: 87)
    - Tret'iakova, Irina (Folder 31: 88)
    - Tret'iakovskaia, Irina (Folder 31: 89)
    - Trinze, Mikhail (Folder 31: 90)
    - Trivus, Anna (Box-folder 32: 1)
    - Trofimov, Vladimir (Folder 32: 2)
    - Troianovskaia, Nataliia (Folder 32: 3)
    - Troshin, Anastasiia, Larisa (Folder 32: 4)
    - Trostianskii, Vadim (Folder 32: 5)
    - Troupianskaia, Izabella (Folder 32: 6)
    - Trubetskoi, Mariia, and Nikolai, and Petr (Folder 32: 7)
    - Trukhachev, Mikhail (Folder 32: 8)
    - Tsenker, Elena (Folder 32: 9)
    - Tsepliaeva, Ol'ga (Folder 32: 10)
    - Tsereteli, Sergei (Folder 32: 11)
    - Tsigler, Ol'ga (Folder 32: 12)
    - Tsikriti, Genrikh (Folder 32: 13)
    - Tsiliga, Pavel (Folder 32: 14)
    - Tsinger, Aleksei (Folder 32: 15)
    - Tsiolkovich, Vsevolod (Folder 32: 16)
    - Tsitron, Lili (Folder 32: 17)
    - Tsitsilin, Vladimir (Folder 32: 18)
    - Tsymbal, Vladimir (Folder 32: 19)
    - Tudakov, Aleksandr (Folder 32: 20)
    - Tunevich, Orest (Folder 32: 21)
    - Turan, Erast (Folder 32: 22)
    - Turkin, Georgii (Folder 32: 23)
    - Turovich, Mikhail (Folder 32: 24)
    - Tutorskaia, Margarita (Folder 32: 25)
    - Tverskoi, Igor' (Folder 32: 26)
    - Udot, Sofiia (Folder 32: 27)
    - Udovkina, Ekaterina, and Nina (Folder 32: 28)
    - Uftiuzaninov, Anatolii (Folder 32: 29)
    - Ulanov, Khongar (Folder 32: 30)
    - Ul'ianitskii, Fedor (Folder 32: 31)
    - Ul'ianov, Iordanka, and Petr, and Stepan (Folder 32: 32)
    - Ungern-Sternberg, Andrei, and Georgii, and Rostislav (Folder 32: 33)
    - Urban-Anshevich, Georgii, and Margarita (Folder 32: 34)
    - Usov, Aleksei (Folder 32: 35)
    - Usol'tseva, Nataliia (Folder 32: 36)
    - Uspenskii, Vladimir (Folder 32: 37)
    - Ustinov, Adrian, and Mikhail, and Nikolai (Folder 32: 38)
    - Vakh, Nataliia von, and Nikolai von (Folder 32: 39)
    - Vakhrushev, Kseniia (Folder 32: 40)
    - Valentinov, Aleksandr (Folder 32: 41)
    - Valichek, Valentin (Folder 32: 42)
    - Valik, Aleksandr (Folder 32: 43)
    - Val'kevich, Boris (Folder 32: 44)
    - Val'nev, Nikolai (Folder 32: 45)
    - Vanyken, Viktor (Folder 32: 46)
    - Varenova, Elena, and Nadezhda (Folder 32: 47)
    - Variagina, Tat'iana (Folder 32: 48)
    - Varnek, E. (Folder 32: 49)
    - Vashadze, Aleksdandr, and Vasilii (Folder 32: 50)
    - Vasil'chikov, Mikhail (Folder 32: 51)
    - Vasil'ev, Igor' (Folder 32: 52)
    - Vasil'ev, Konstantin (Folder 32: 53)
    - Vasil'ev, Mikhail (Folder 32: 54)
    - Vasil'ev, Viacheslav (Folder 32: 55)
    - Vasil'eva, Irina (Folder 32: 56)
    - Veber, Azarii (Folder 32: 57)
    - Veen, Georgii, van (Folder 32: 58)
    - Veidle, Dmitrii (Folder 32: 59)
    - Veil, Nikolai (Folder 32: 60)
    - Veis, Igor' (Folder 32: 61)
    - Vel'kevich, Boris (Folder 32: 62)
    - Vel's, Nikita (Folder 32: 63)
    - Venuti, Nikolai (Folder 32: 64)
    - Verkhovskoi, Iurii (Folder 32: 65)
    - Vernik, Igor' (Folder 32: 66)
    - Vershinina, Nina, and Ol'ga (Folder 32: 67)
    - Vesnin, Georgii (Folder 32: 68)
    - Vestfal, Pavel (Folder 32: 69)
    - Vetrov, Georgii (Folder 32: 70)
    - Vigand, Leonid (Folder 32: 71)
    - Vignera, Lidiia (Folder 32: 72)
    - Vikulov, Aleksandr, and Vera (Folder 32: 73)
    - Vil'de, Nataliia, and Ol'ga (Folder 32: 74)
    - Vinogradov, Leonid, and Mark (Folder 32: 75)
    - Vinogradov, Anastasiia, and Kseniia, and Liudmila, and Tat'iana (Folder 32: 76)
    - Vinokurov, Aleksandr (Folder 32: 77)
    - Vinterfel'd, Dimitrii, and Irina (Folder 32: 78)
    - Virenius, N. (Folder 32: 79)
    - Vishnevskaia, Nataliia, and Zinaida (Folder 32: 80)
    - Vilt, Ol'ga, de (Box-folder 33: 1)
    - Vitt, Tat'iana (Folder 33: 2)
    - Vlasenko, Iurii (Folder 33: 3)
    - Vlasov, Aleksei (Folder 33: 4)
    - Vlasova, Ol'ga (Folder 33: 5)
    - Vnarovskii, Anna, and Vladimir (Folder 33: 6)
    - Voichenkov, Konstantin (Folder 33: 7)
    - Voinov, Boris (Folder 33: 8)
    - Voinovich, Igor' (Folder 33: 9)
    - Volikovskii, Viktor (Folder 33: 10)
    - Volkenshtein, Fedor (Folder 33: 11)
    - Volkonskii, Andrei, and Daniil, and Mikhail, and Nadezhda, and Nataliia (Folder 33: 12)
    - Volkov, Dimitrii (Folder 33: 13)
    - Volkov, Evgenii (Folder 33: 14)
    - Volkov, Ivan (Folder 33: 15)
    - Volkov, Pavel (Folder 33: 16)
    - Volkova, Nadezhda (Folder 33: 17)
    - Volkovysskii, Viktor (Folder 33: 18)
    - Voloshin, Pavel (Folder 33: 19)
    - Volovich, Grigorii (Folder 33: 20)
    - Volynskaia, Nataliia (Folder 33: 21)
    - Vol'f, Andrei (Folder 33: 22)
    - Vorlichek, Boris (Folder 33: 23)
    - Voronkovskaia, Ol'ga (Folder 33: 24)
    - Voronov, Aleksandr, and Elena (Folder 33: 25)
    - Vorontsev, Aleksei (Folder 33: 26)
    - Vorontsov, Mikhail (Folder 33: 27)
    - Vorontsov-Dashkov, Aleksandr, and Illarion, and Mikhail, and Tat'iana (Folder 33: 28)
    - Vozdvizhenskaia, Ol'ga (Folder 33: 29)
    - Vsevolzhskaia, Irina (Folder 33: 30)
    - Vurgaft, Mariia (Folder 33: 31)
    - Vurgaft, Tamara (Folder 33: 32)
    - Vutsin, Aleksandr, and Evgenii, and Liudmila (Folder 33: 33)
    - Vysokopol'skii, Aleksei (Folder 33: 34)
    - Vysokosova, Mariia (Folder 33: 35)
    - Vysotskii, Iurii (Folder 33: 36)
    - Walton, Tat'iana (Folder 33: 37)
    - Zabudskii, Vladimir (Folder 33: 38)
    - Zade, Marc, and Valiia (Folder 33: 39)
    - Zagrebel'skaia, Ol'ga (Folder 33: 40)
    - Zaichik, Grigorii (Folder 33: 41)
    - Zaitsev, Ivan (Folder 33: 42)
    - Zaitsev, Galina, and Iuliia, and Mariia (Folder 33: 43)
    - Zakharchenko, Karp, and Vladimir, and Vladimir (Folder 33: 44)
    - Zakharov, Boris (Folder 33: 45)
    - Zalkind, Arii (Folder 33: 46)
    - Zal'tsberg, Garri-Lev (Folder 33: 47)
    - Zamaiskaia, Elizaveta, Viktoriia (Folder 33: 48)
    - Zamaiskii, Elizaveta, Nikolai, and Tamara, and Vera (Folder 33: 49)
    - Zapol'skii, Sergei (Folder 33: 50)
    - Zarochentseva, Ekaterina, and Irina (Folder 33: 51)
    - Zaushupina, Irina (Folder 33: 52)
    - Zavadovskii, Georgii (Folder 33: 53)
    - Zaval'shin, Sergei (Folder 33: 54)
    - Zavediia, Grigorii (Folder 33: 55)
    - Zazunova, Anna, and Margarita, and Nina (Folder 33: 56)
    - Zborovskaia, Marina (Folder 33: 57)
    - Zelenskaia, Anna, and Elizaveta (Folder 33: 58)
    - Zelinger, Fillip, and Rudol'f (Folder 33: 59)
    - Zenevich, Liudmila (Folder 33: 60)
    - Zen'kovich, Serafim (Folder 33: 61)
    - Zernov, Nikolai (Folder 33: 62)
    - Zhdanov, Alla, and Iurii, and Nataliia, and Nikita, and Vadim (Folder 33: 63)
    - Zhdanovich, Boris, and Mariia, and Tat'iana (Folder 33: 64)
    - Zhestokova, Elena (Folder 33: 65)
    - Zhevanov, Andrei (Folder 33: 66)
    - Zhidkov, Nikolai (Folder 33: 67)
    - Zhidkov, Oleg (Folder 33: 68)
    - Zhiliaev, Nikolai (Folder 33: 69)
    - Zhitkov, Boris (Folder 33: 70)
    - Zhivolup, Vladimir (Folder 33: 71)
    - Zholtovskaia, Rakhil' (Folder 33: 72)
    - Zhuk, Dimitrii, and Vladimir (Folder 33: 73)
    - Zhukov, Andrei, and Liudmila, and Nikolai, and Vladimir (Folder 33: 74)
    - Ziberov, Nikita (Folder 33: 75)
    - Zil'berberg, Abram (Folder 33: 76)
    - Zilov, Vladimir (Folder 33: 77)
    - Zimina, Anna (Folder 33: 78)
    - Zin'kovskaia, Favsta (Folder 33: 79)
    - Znachkovskii, Vladimir (Folder 33: 80)
    - Zolotorenko, Suzanna, Vladimir (Folder 33: 81)
    - Zolotovskii, Sergei (Folder 33: 82)
    - Zolotukhina, Nataliia, Irina (Folder 33: 83)
    - Zolynskii, Anatolii (Box-folder 34: 1)
    - Zozulia, Aleksei (Folder 34: 2)
    - Zozulina, Irina (Folder 34: 3)
    - Zubchenko, Ekaterina (Folder 34: 4)
    - Zvegintsev, Nikita (Folder 34: 5)
    - Zvegintsov, Mikhail (Folder 34: 6)
  - Subject file, 1920-1965 and undated
    - Lawsuit, 1950-1962. (Folder 34: 7)
      Includes related correspondence, minutes of meetings, and notes
    - Nedachin, Vasilii Pavlovich, 1933 (Folder 34: 8)
    - Obshchestvo prosveshcheniia detei bezhentsev iz Rossii
      - Annual reports, 1921-1922 (Folder 34: 9)
      - Correspondence, 1922-1951 and undated (Folder 34: 10)
      - Financial reports (Folder 34: 11)
      - Minutes of meetings
        - 1920-1925 and undated (Folder 34: 12)
        - 1926-1929 (Folder 34: 13)
        - 1930-1938 (Folder 34: 14)
        - 1930-1940 (Box-folder 35: 1)
        - 1940-1960 (Folder 35: 2)
        - 1960-1961 (Folder 35: 3)
        - 1965 (Folder 35: 4)
      - Statute (Folder 35: 5)
      - Miscellany. (Folder 35: 6)
        Includes official letterhead
    - Romanov, House of., See also Office file/Student records/Kulikovskii, Gurii, Tikhon (Folder 35: 7)
    - Miscellany, 193?-1960 and undated. (Folder 35: 8)
      Includes blank certificates and diplomas
- Photographs, 1928-1949 and undated. (Folder 35: 9)
  Twenty-three prints of teachers and pupils
- Oversize file, 1921-1927. (Box 36)
  Twelve certificates of graduation